So here's how I created a custom estimator that utilizes a training script.
下面说说我是如何创建一个利用训练脚本的自定义 estimator 的
First, I've inputted the PyTorch Estimator from sagemaker.pytorch.
首先我从 sagemaker.pytorch 导入了 PyTorch Estimator
Then, I'm going to specify an output path in
然后指定输出路径
s3 where I want my trained model to be saved,
表示我要将训练过的模型保存到 S3 上的哪个位置
and then I'm creating an estimator passing in a number of constructor arguments.
然后创建一个 estimator 并传入几个构造函数参数
Now, let's first take a look at the PyTorch estimator documentation.
先打开 PyTorch estimator 文档
In here, I can see that this takes in an entry point,
从这里可以看到 estimator 的参数包括入口点
a source directory, and several hyperparameters including a framework version.
源目录以及几个超参数 包括框架版本
If I scroll down, I can see that the entry point is a path to the Python source file,
向下滚动 可以看到入口点是指 Python 源文件的路径
which will be executed as the entry point to training.
它将执行并作为训练的入口点
The source directory is a directory with any other training source code dependencies.
源目录是指包含任何其他训练源代码依赖项的目录
In this case, this will be our source directory
现在它将是保存了
where our model that PY file is also saved.
model.py 文件的源目录
The hyperparameters are things that we defined in our argument parser,
超参数是指在参数解析器中指定的项
and the framework version is
框架版本是指
just the PyTorch version you want to use for executing your model.
在执行模型时你希望使用的 PyTorch 版本
So here, I've specified an entry point,
我指定了入口点
my training script and a source directory where that can be found.
训练脚本以及源代码所在的目录
Since I'm demonstrating a solution,
因为我演示的是解决方案
I'm using the code that's complete in source_solution.
所以使用了 source_solution 中的代码
But for you, if you've worked on a train.py file of your own,
但是如果你自己完成了 train.py 文件
you should be able to use just source and your complete train.py file.
你可以在这里设为 source 并使用你完成的 train.py 文件
Then, I'm specifying my usual SageMaker parameters including
然后指定常规的 SageMaker 参数
role and things about my trained instance and sagemaker_session.
包括角色和训练实例以及 SageMaker 会话
I'm also thinking that I want to use the latest version of PyTorch,
我想使用最新版 PyTorch
which at this recording is Version 1.0.
在录制本视频时为版本 1.0
Here, I'm specifying my model and training hyperparameters.
我在这里指定了模型和训练超参数
I know I have two-dimensional input data and we're specifying the number of
我知道输入数据是二维的
hidden nodes which will hopefully be
并且指定了隐藏节点的数量
complex enough to help me find the patterns in this data,
希望模型够复杂 能够发现数据中的模式
and I want to output one value as output.
我希望输出是一个值
I have also specified that I want to train this model for 80 epochs.
并且指定要训练 80 个周期
Now, during actual training,
在实际训练过程中
I'll note the model loss and see if I could train for longer,
我将观察模型损失
that is if the loss continues to decrease or if it became plateaus,
如果损失继续下降 则训练更长时间
in which case I want to decrease this number.
如果损失停滞不变 则减少训练周期
So I've created a custom PyTorch estimator and the next thing
我已经创建了自定义 PyTorch estimator
I want to do is train that estimator on my training data.
下一步是使用训练数据训练该 estimator
If you recall in the training script,
在训练脚本中
our trained data loader explicitly accepted a CSV file as
训练数据加载器明确要求输入是 csv 文件
input with labels in the first column of data and features in the rest of the columns.
第一列是标签 其余列是特征
So we do not need to take any further steps to
所以我们不需要进一步处理
format the train.csv file that we stored in s3 earlier.
之前存储到 S3 上的 train.csv 文件
Our custom estimator will accept the CSV file just as it is,
自定义 estimator 将直接接受该 csv 文件
and instead of passing in only the data,
除了传入数据之外
I'll pass in a dictionary that specifies that
还将传入一个字典
this data is to be treated as data in the train channel.
指定该数据将在训练渠道中处理
Then this kicks off a training job with this name.
这样就会启动具有这个名称的训练作业
I can see my instance being spun up and details about my model parameters.
可以看到实例在运行以及模型参数详细信息
For example, I should see that my transcript is
例如应该看到训练脚本被调用
invoked with my specified number of epochs,
并且设为指定的周期数
hidden dimension, input dimension, and output dimension.
隐藏维度 输入维度和输出维度
Then, my twin loop prints out my average training loss after each epoch,
然后 训练循环将在每个周期之后输出平均训练损失
and I should see this decrease.
应该看到损失在下降
So at Epoch 80,
在第 80 个周期
I see that it's decreased from about 0.8-0.4,
损失从 0.8 下降到了 0.4
and it looks like it's slowly but surely still decreasing.
看起来下降速度很慢 但是依然在下降
So I could have set it to train for longer.
所以可以设为训练更长时间
So now we've done a lot,
我们完成了很多步骤
from defining the customer estimator to training that estimator here.
从定义自定义 estimator 到训练该 estimator
Now, there's one extra step before I can deploy this and make predictions.
在部署该 estimator 并作出预测之前 还有一步要完成
You may have noticed that in previous examples like when I call.deploy on linear learner,
你可能注意到了 在之前的示例中 当我对 LinearLearner 调用 .deploy 时
two things happened; a linear learner model was created and an endpoint was created.
发生了两项操作 系统创建了 LinearLearner 模型并且创建了端点
In the case of a custom PyTorch model,
对于自定义 PyTorch 模型
I'll need to create a model and an endpoint individually.
我需要单独创建模型和端点
PyTorch models do not automatically come with.predict functions.
PyTorch 模型并没有自动内置 .predict 函数
You may have noticed earlier that you were given a predict.py file.
你可能注意到了 我们提供了 predict.py 文件
This file is responsible for loading in
此文件负责加载训练过的模型
a trained model and applying it to paste in data to produce predictions.
并将其应用到传入的数据上以生成预测
Much like an estimator knew where the transcript was,
就像 estimator 知道训练脚本在哪一样
the next task will be to create a PyTorch model that knows where this predict.py file is.
下个任务是创建一个知道这个 predict.py 文件在哪的 PyTorch 模型
A PyTorch model takes in a few constructor arguments including an entry point,
一个 PyTorch 模型需要几个构造函数参数
which in this case will be our predict.py file.
包括入口点 这里是我们的 predict.py 文件
It also takes in the trained estimator data,
还需要训练过的 estimator 数据
the trained model attributes.
即训练的模型属性
This is the zipped model file that we use to explore model attributes earlier,
它是压缩模型文件 我们之前通过它探索模型属性
and it's also used to deploy a model.
并且用来部署模型
When an estimator is trained,
训练 estimator 后
you can get it with a call to estimator.model_data.
你可以通过调用 estimator.model_data 获取该 estimator
So try to create this model on your own and deploy it.
请试着自己创建并部署此模型
If you get this far, you can use
如果你完成了这些任务
your deployed predictor and see how it performs on some test data.
可以将部署的预测器应用到测试数据上 看看效果如何
In the next video, I'll show you one possible solution along with some test results.
在下个视频中 我将演示一种解决方案以及一些测试结果